Guide to the Screamers collection, circa 1963-1981.
Screamers collection,
- Posters and fliers, 1974-1979
  - Screamers Show at Mabuhay Gardens, 1978-06-25-1978-06-26; Collaged flier with white out edits, original master copy to be Xeroxed into fliers (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Screamers Show at the Whisky a Go-Go, 1978-05-17-1978-05-19; Original master copy with white out edits (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Screamers benefit concert, 1978-05-18; Black and red paper (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Portland, Oregon
  - Screamers Show at the Whisky a Go-Go, 1978-04-13-1978-04-15; Gary Panter logo. (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Sold Out, 122 Hours premiere
  - Screamers Show at the Whisky a Go-Go, 1979-05-17-1979-05-19 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Screamers with Weirdos and Crime at Stardust Ballroom, 1978-07-03 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Screamers Poster, 1979; Gary Panter logo, screen print (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Screamers with Lounge Lizards at Hurrah, 1979-07-05-1979-07-08; G. Panter logo. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Screamers Show at the Rat, 1978-11-08 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Boston, Massachusetts
  - Screamers at The Whisky, 1978-07-20-1978-07-22 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Art by Gary Panter
  - Screamers, Tuxedomoon, and The Units at California Hall, 1979-05-25 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Flier advertises concert as well as radio shows, presented by Bill Graham and Ksan’s Heretics
  - Screamers Show at the Starwood, 1977-07-04; Annotated on bottom left corner, “Photo: Melanie Nissen” (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Offset lithographs
  - Screamers Show at Strata Head, 1978-03-25; Featuring Gary Panter “Screamers image.” Annotated on verso, “Tomata – Your friends from Seattle are here. Went down to Cantaberry for a while and will return soon. And your friend from Van Nuys came and went. He was in a poetic and exciting inspirational positive force space sourcing real – Bring Bruce! … Old At the Errol Flynn Estate Bring Hot Dogs!” Xeroxed. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    San Diego, California
  - Screamers Show at the Whisky a Go-Go, 1978-04-13-1978-04-15; Cut and paste collage (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Screamers ‘Nazi’ flier, Mabuhay Gardens, 1978-07-15-1978-07-16; Black and white, white out edits, master copy original flier (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Screamers Show at the Whisky a Go-Go (two shows nightly), 1978-07-20-1978-07-22; Original mock up flier collage with tape and clippings (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Screamers Show at the Whisky a Go-Go, 1979-05-17-1979-05-19; Original print uncut (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Possibly uncirculated
  - Screamers X-Mas flier, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Autographed by Tomata, KK, and Tommy Xeroxed. Melanie Nissen photo of the band
  - Screamers Show at the Whisky a Go-Go, 1978-04-13-1978-04-15; Gary Panter logo (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Screamers and Weirdos at the Masque, 1977-12-16 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Jeff McGregor’s first show
  - Screamers with Weirdos and Crime at the Masque (Stardust Ballroom), 1977-07-03; Lesperance, Paul (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Screamers Show at the Starwood, 1977-07-04; Handmade original copy, silkscreen, stencil, paint (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Gary Panter “shrieking head” Screamers logo, 1970-1979 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Weirdos and Screamers at the Masque, 1977-12-16 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Presented by Slash Magazine.
  - Screamers with Lounge Lizards, 1979-07-05-1979-07-08; Round Gary Panter logo (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Screamers Show at the Whisky a Go-Go, 1978-07-20-1978-07-22; Gary Panter logo, pink and black silk screen. First time unsigned band sold out three shows at the Whisky (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - “Do the Whisky”, 1978-06-21 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Screen prints
  - Screamers with The Original Biblical Gospel Singers at the Roxys, 1979-07-19-1979-07-21; 3 color screen print, round Gary Panter logo (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Screamers at Hurrah, 1978-11-03 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    With Gary Panter logo. Offset
  - Screamers with Lounge Lizards at Hurrah, 1979-07-05-1979-07-08 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Black and red text with Gary Banter logo.
  - Screamers ‘Do the Whisky’ at Whisky a Go-Go, 1978-06-21; Colored in with marker (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Screen print
  - The Palm Casino Revue, 1974-05; The logo and show details framed by vignettes of the cast, which includes Tomata du Plenty second up from the bottom right. Black and white. (Map-case map-case, Folder 1)
- Publicity and press materials, 1963-2001
  - Magazines, clippings, and zines, 1977-2001
    Featuring articles on the Screamers or on punk.
    - Apache Magazine, No. 9, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Nude “Punk Girl” spread and early Brooke Shields photos
      Japan
    - Best Magazine, Vol. 10, No. 120, 1978-07 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      French magazine: Iggy, Ramones, Buzzcocks, Clash
    - The Big Takeover Magazine, Issue 47, Vol. XXI, No. 2, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - The Big Takeover Magazine, Issue 48, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Tribute to Tomata who recently passed away: interview, pictures and more
    - JD Magazine, No. 1, 1978-06-10; Staple bound. (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Interview with Tommy Gear, photocopy of set list from 5/18/78 Portland, OR. Show.
    - Synapse Magazine: Vol. 2, No. 3, 1977-11-12; Burk, Greg (Box 2, Folder 3)
      pg. 7: ‘Performance’ article and photo – ‘Synthesizers Pollute the New Wave’
    - Violent World Magazine, 1977-08 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Article on “Blood Rock” or punk/bloody music/art. pg. 34-35 photos of Iggy and Alice Cooper
    - The Upsetter, no. 1, 1978; YoYo Youths Graphics, ed. (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Punk zine featuring X, Alley Cats, Flesh Eaters, Alice Bag Band, and others. 23pp.
    - Screamers, 1979-01-06; Savage, John; 16 pages, 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Typescript of article published in Melody Maker.
    - The Punk Scene, 1977; Full color poster book (Sex Pistols photos, the Clash photos and poster, Stranglers photos) (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Joyride, No. 1, 1970-1979; Staple bound zine. (Box 3, Folder 15)
      ‘Peer Pressure’ lyrics and Fan Club application.
    - The Privateer Magazine, vol. 1, 1977-10 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - CREEM Magazine, 1977-12; Basher, Jack (Box 3, Folder 15)
      pg. 36-40 ‘Catch a Wave? No West Coast New Wave’, Screamers photos on pg. 36, article on pg. 59
    - Variety Magazine Japan, 1970-1979 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      ‘Punk Rock in LA’ rare photos. Color Xeroxed clippings
    - Bob Morris’ Records Magazine, No. 10, 1976-11 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Surfin’ Bird, No. 2, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      Montreal rock zine. Screamers on cover, interview w/ Tomata, ‘Night Out with the Screamers’ article. Staple bound
    - The National Observer, 1977-06-27 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      ’The Music they Call Punk Rock’ clipping, 2 pg.
    - New York Rocker, Vol. 1, No. 9, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      Newspaper clipping pasted on white paper
    - The San Francisco Progress, 1977-07-31 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      Screamers review, article bashing the scene. Clipping pasted on white paper
    - Twisted Magazine, 1977-05-28 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      Screamers review and article clipping, pg. 1-4, debut feature for band
    - Melody Maker, Vol. 52, No. 30, 1977-07-23; Kubernik, Harvey (Box 3, Folder 17)
      American music write up/clipping
    - Seattle Newspaper, 1978-05-19; MacDonald, Patrick (Box 3, Folder 18)
      ‘Unusual Bills Fill Weekend’ clipping. Carpenter’s Hall, Seattle.
    - Los Angeles Times, 1979-05-22 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      Whisky review and photo, newspaper clipping with white out and tape
    - University of Washington Daily, 1978-05; Wilson, John L. (Box 3, Folder 18)
      ‘The Screamers Meet Eva Braun’ clipping
    - The Montreal Star, 1978-01-21; de Lotbiniere, Susanne (Box 3, Folder 18)
      ‘California Punkin’ profile - Harwood, newspaper clipping
    - Melody Maker, 1979-01-06; Savage, Jon (Box 3, Folder 18)
      ‘The New Wave Laps on Terminal Beach’, two page spread
    - Variety Magazine, No. 2, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      ‘Punk Rock in LA’ pg. 127
    - Screamers Fan Club Zine, No. 1, 1977-07; Staple bound. (Box 3, Folder 19)
      Includes photos, interviews, questionnaires.
    - Screamers Fan Club Zine, No. 2, 1977; Hand colored “Screamers” in marker on cover. Staple bound, Xeroxed (Box 3, Folder 19)
      Cover photo by Diane Grave.
    - Screamers Fan Club Zine No. 2, 1977; Half of zine staple bound (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Newspapers and clippings, 1963-1981
    - BAM Magazine, 1979-07-01 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      Clipping of Screamers Whisky review
    - BAM Magazine, 1978-05-05 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      Photo and article, pg. 45 and 47
    - The Guardian Newspaper, 1970-12-05 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - The Guardian Newspaper, 1970-11-28 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - The Guardian Newspaper, 1970-11-14 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - The Guardian Newspaper, 1970-10-17 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - The Guardian Newspaper, 1970-08-15 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - The Guardian Newspaper, 1970-10-03 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - The Guardian Newspaper, 1970-09-26 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - The Guardian Newspaper, 1970-08-08 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Helix Magazine, Vol.10, No.4, 1969-10-30 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Helix Magazine, Vol.10, No. 11, 1969-12-18 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Helix Magazine, Vol.7, No. 10, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Helix Magazine, Vol.11, No. 5, 1970-01-29 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - HELIX, Vol. 9, No. 8, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - HELIX, Vol. 9, No. 4, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Hollywood Press: A Sexual Freedom Publication, vol. Vl, no. 11, issue 236, 1977-05-26; Taylor, Bob; 2 copies (Box 5, Folder 4)
      pg. 6, photo and article on Screamers.
    - Hollywood Press: A Sexual Freedom Publication, vol. Vl, no. 16, issue 16, 1977-07-08; Taylor, Bob; 2 copies (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Screamers Scream Again, 1981-07-05; Spurrier, Jeff (Box 5, Folder 5)
      LA Weekly article clipping
    - Los Angeles Herald Examiner, 1981-07-11 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Palace of Variety review (style section)
    - Los Angeles Times, 1979-05-22 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Primal Screams at the Whisky
    - Los Angeles Times, 1978-02-28 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Clipping of Screamers Showcase review
    - Los Angeles Times, 1981-07-11 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Palace of Variety review
    - Los Angeles Times, 1978-07-02 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Screamers photo and write up, pg. 66-67
    - Los Angeles Times, 1978-06-07
      Screamers review and Positivity in Punk article
    - NME, 1975-08-30 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - NME, 1975-08-23 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - New York Rocker, 1977-09-1977-10 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - National Observer, 1977-06-27 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Featuring Screamers on front page
    - The Picture Newspaper, Vol. IV, No. 3, 1975-11-03 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - The Picture Newspaper, Part Two, 1975-12-1976-01 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - RE Search Zine, No. 1, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - RE Search Zine, No. 2, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - RE Search Zine, No. 3, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Search and Destroy No. 2, 1977-09 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Featuring Tomata on cover. Full 2 pg. interview w/ band after 12/19/77 Mabuhay Gardens show in San Francisco show. Poster of Tommy Gear. Photo by Ruby Ray
    - The Seattle Times/Tempo, 1978-05-19 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      pg. 6 ad for show
    - Tolo, vol. 50, no. 10, 1970-02-24; 3 copies (Box 4, Folder 4)
      pg. 7, photo of Tommy Tibbits.
    - Tolo, vol. 50, no. 11, 1970-03-17 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Tolo, vol. 50, no. 12, 1970-04-14; 2 copies (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Tolo, vol. 50, no. 13, 1970-05-07; Tibbits, Tommy (Box 4, Folder 5)
      pg. 2, Letter to the Editor: Postscript to Earth Day
    - Tolo, vol. 50, no. 14, 1970-05-19 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Tolo, vol. 51, no. 2, 1970-09-22 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Tolo, vol. 51, no. 3, 1970-10-12 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Tolo, vol. 51, no. 4, 1970-10-27; Tibbits, Tommy (Box 4, Folder 5)
      pg. 8 ‘Expresso Yourself ’ article on coffee shops in Seattle
    - Tolo, vol. 51, no. 8, 1971-02-09 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - University of Washington Daily Paper, No. 101, 1970-05-05 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - University of Washington Daily, 1978-05-26; Wilson, John L. (Box 6, Folder 2)
      ‘The Screamers Meet Eva Braun’ clipping. May 26, 1978 handwritten in top right corner
    - Weekender - San Gabriel Valley Daily Tribune, 1978-08-04 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      2 page spread on "Punk"
  - Kennedy assination and Pope John XXIII
    - The Spokesman Review Newspaper, 1963-11-23 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Kennedy assassination front page
      Spokane, Washington
    - Seattle Daily Times, 1963-11-22 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Kennedy assassination
    - Seattle Daily Times, 1963-11-24 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      D section - Kennedy photo retrospective
    - Seattle Daily Times, 1963-11-25 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Kennedy funeral, Jackie O at casket
    - Seattle Daily Times, 1963-06-03 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      Death of Pope John XXlll
    - The Catholic Northwest Progress, 1963-06-07 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - The Catholic Northwest Progress, 1963-11-29 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      Kennedy eulogy and drawing
    - Seattle Post Intelligencer, 1963-11-22 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Seattle Post Intelligencer, 1963-11-23 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      Kennedy assassination and LBJ swear in
    - W Newspaper, Vol. 5, No. 15, 1976-07-23-1976-07-30 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Seattle Daily Times, 1964-03-30 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      Kodiak earthquake and tidal wave
    - Seattle Post Intelligencer, 1963-04-07 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      100th anniversary issue
  - Publicity and press releases, 1978-1979
    - Publicity - IDEAS, Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
      Folder containing various scraps of paper with contact information handwritten, clippings from magazines and newspapers, business cards, and “Chronological History”. Typed and Xeroxed, edited by hand portion of their press kit with a history of the bands’ activities
    - Screamers Show at the Rat, 1978-11-08 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Screamers shows at Hotel Nelson, 1978-11-11-1978-11-12; Mimeograph brown ink (Box 2, Folder 6)
      Montreal, Canada
    - Screamers Press Kit, 1979; Staple Bound. (Box 2, Folder 6)
      Gary Panter logo on cover. Includes articles, photos, contacts, etc.
    - Screamers Show at Horseshoe Tavern, 1970-1979; Typed. Screamers Fan Club application on verso. (Box 2, Folder 6)
      Photo by Ken Banks.
      Toronto, Canada
    - Screamers shows at Hotel Nelson, 1978-11 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Screamers press release template, 1970-1979 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      Including date, location, venue, phone number (all blank)
    - Interview questions, Undated; Handwritten on notebook paper (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Press clippings and quotes, Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - List of Publications Which Have Featured the Screamers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Specifies whether it is a photo, essay or interview. Typed
    - Screamers at the Roxy, 1979-07-19-1979-07-21; Typed (Box 2, Folder 7)
      2 press releases (added quotes, including Andy Warhol)
    - Press Release for first West Coast Screamers tour, Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
      One copy, one original
    - Press release for 7/3 Screamers show at Stardust Ballroom, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - BAM Magazine, 1978; Taylor, Bob (Box 2, Folder 7)
      4/7/78 pre published article, published on 5/5/ 78
    - Screamers Return to New York, 1979; Typed (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Announcement of shows at Hurrah’s 7/5- 7/8/79.
    - Press Release of first West Coast Screamers tour, Undated; 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 7)
      G. Panter logo as header.
    - Screamers at the Roxy, 1979; 5 copies (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Press release for 7/19-21/79 shows at the Roxy.
    - List of publications sent a Screamers press kit, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Slash, Creem, Twisted, LA Times
    - Screamers Fans Unite, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Fan Club application form
    - Screamers Fan Club Zine #1, Undated; Loose pages. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Various Xeroxed press clippings for packet, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Screamers press kit (Box 2, Folder 8)
      20x pg., clippings, photos, press articles, concert reviews
    - Screamers press packet, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Screamers Original Press Kit Layout, 1979; Original master copy flier, pre-Xerox, cut and paste (Box 4, Folder 7)
      Roxy in Los Angeles, 7/ 19- 7/21/79, Gary Panter logo, created on Hustler Humor and Slam Magazine paper stock
      3 x mini Gary Panter Screamers logo and title, business cards/tickets, 2 uncut, 1 cut, and on Hustler Humor and Slam Magazine paper stock
      Screamers booking phone number, back page of press kit, print glued to on uncut magazine stock